Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The world decays, in gloom I stray♪
♪Right and wrong, in frost engraved♪
♪On dreams of love, blades clash and sway♪
♪Alone I ride, blood still unswayed♪
♪Through heaven's mirth and earth's despair♪
♪Toasting the moon, I drink the chill air♪
♪Though hearts like battlefields may be♪
♪Let fate write its uncertainty♪
♪From this life to the great unknown♪
♪Who'll stand with me, on thrones unknown?♪
♪I'll wander through this life to guard you♪
♪Through mortal realms, serene I roam♪
♪With you, the world becomes my home♪
♪Unbroken, bold, as I have sworn♪
♪I'll roam this life, and feel no torn♪
♪Our souls embraced, no regret born♪
♪By twilight's lamp, though night be worn♪
♪Through deepest dark, I'll find the morn♪
=Fight For Love=
=Episode 35=
I hate to see Zhang Deng like that.
I want to kick him.
We came on horseback.
Why is it a carriage now?
Perhaps Ms. Chu was worried
that you'd be uncomfortable
riding a horse,
so she asked Wanyue
to arrange a carriage.
Get in.
Why is it broken?
Young Master,
I just went to relieve myself.
When I came back, it was like this.
I'm not being suspicious,
but now that you're the Chancellor,
someone is bound to be envious.
It wasn't me.
Don't worry.
If it were Wei Qiu,
he wouldn't have been so gentle.
You'd have lost the carriage
and shafts.
How about this?
I'll give you a ride.
Sure.
You're so kind.
How can I refuse?
Zhang Deng, you go back.
Your Lordship, Chancellor Gu.
Please.
These are all carefully prepared
by Ms. Chu for His Lordship.
Even these minor details
were personally taken care of.
When I get back,
I'll thank Yu properly.
I like everything she prepared.
Chancellor Gu,
you'll have to bear with me
and follow my preferences.
It's Zisun tea.
Would you like to try some?
No need.
I'm not used to this tea.
Let me see what else is prepared.
I'm so sorry.
I have unique tastes.
If there's nothing
that suits your taste...
Just drink more water.
You don't need to put on a show
in front of me.
You've given up the power
that comes with being second to none,
and you can't marry Yu
in this life.
It's all in vain.
I feel sorry for you.
Now, you are truly
second to none.
So, you should focus more
on the people.
As you wish.
I won't stoop to your level.
As long
as I have this dessert
prepared by her for me,
that's enough.
Since we don't see eye to eye,
let's just stop talking.
Your Lordship, look!
- So many butterflies.
- Look.
It's made of paper.
In this world,
only she could come up
with so many quirky ideas.
Chancellor Gu,
I have to go.
Sorry about stopping here.
Xiaoqi,
do you think he'll like
the surprise I prepared for him?
No matter what,
I just hope he can be happier
and more at ease.
Isn't that right?
Such a grand
and elaborate display,
with so many new tricks.
You're amazing.
Are you pleased?
It's been a long time
since I laughed so heartily,
but I'm also afraid
that these happy days
won't last long.
Tomorrow,
let's visit the Duke of Hu
to see
if he has any solutions.
Caught in the whirlpool of the court,
we are but a cocoon.
It's either binding ourselves in it
or being shattered to pieces.
Fortunately, with your company,
I hope we can break free
and become a butterfly.
(Spring Breeze House)
Welcome, please come in.
Alright.
Today,
I should call you Chancellor Gu.
Gu,
you've brought your family
back into the public eye,
and you've returned
to the position your father once held.
That's not easy.
We're happy for you.
You two,
don't be formal with me.
Chusheng,
we've seen your determination
and ability.
Most importantly,
your courage to burn your boats
is truly admirable.
I'd be content
if I could clear my family's name.
Your family's grievances
have come to an end.
However, the current situation
has become very delicate.
How so?
In the battles of Qingzhou and Fengling,
Wei Yun made the most contribution.
Yet the Emperor has neglected him
and lost faith in him.
Young Marquis Wei, acting on impulse,
has ruined his future.
He's disregarded
the Emperor's authority.
The Emperor has given him a chance,
but he refused to grasp
this imperial favor.
If you say it that way,
the situation is indeed delicate.
The Emperor values the balance
between civil and military officials.
Now, with Chusheng on the civil side,
the military...
Shilan,
if it were you,
what would you do?
I'm willing to bear that burden.
(Gu Mansion)
Why are you here?
Can I have a chat with you?
I know that my father's safe return
to his hometown
must have been thanks
to your help.
Today,
I've come to thank you.
No need.
On the day of our divorce,
I promised
to do one thing for you.
This is fulfilling that promise.
Ms. Wang,
did you come here just for this?
Seeing you speak
in front of me,
it feels like we're back
in the old days.
Though
we are no longer married,
we are still old acquaintances.
Mr. Gu,
you'd at least let me
finish speaking, right?
We've been divorced.
Unless necessary,
we won't meet again.
What about her?
With a single imperial decree,
the Emperor has forever fixed Chu Yu
in the position of Mrs. Wei.
You've calculated everything,
but you didn't anticipate this, right?
That title means
she can never remarry.
You wanted to use the Emperor
to break them apart,
but you lost her, too.
Cleverness has backfired.
Do you have anything else to say?
During my visit today,
I've said all the good
and bad words I wanted to say.
It's indeed time for me to leave.
I remember
that your birthday is coming up.
Chancellor Gu, I wish you
a long
and solitary life.
(Yifen Hall)
Zhao Yue is not available today,
so it's you who'll accompany me?
As someone without a title or status,
I'm truly honored.
Your way of treating guests
in North Qi is quite intriguing.
As a woman,
I naturally understand
the loneliness in the Palace.
You spend all your days here.
I feel sorry for you.
So, I came to tell you
some interesting stories from outside.
Beautiful but not seductive;
gorgeous but not vulgar.
No wonder Yue is so captivated by you.
Stop beating around the bush.
I don't think
that compared to handling state affairs,
you prefer to be here,
sparring with me.
How boring.
Yue's father was from Great Sui.
In the eyes of the people of North Qi,
he is less than an illegitimate child.
Yet no one stopped Yue
from ascending the throne.
Do you know why?
It's because of my support.
I even arranged for Yue
to marry two consorts
to stabilize his kingship.
Today is the day of Yue's wedding
with Noble Consort Chen.
You once seduced the Lord of Qin
and got
three cities from him.
As a ruler, Zhao Yue
also has to rely on selling his charm
to secure his kingdom.
Like mother, like son.
Didn't you also use
a marriage deal to secure
the throne
for your brother?
To achieve a goal,
I'll do anything.
That is my resolve.
I will not allow anyone
to stop Yue
from becoming an emperor.
Zhao Yue now needs to rely
on marriage alliances
to stabilize his throne,
which shows that your position
in North Qi is also unstable.
If you kill me,
aren't you afraid
that Great Sui will come after you?
Emperor Chunde is weak and sickly.
Crown Prince Li Huan is incompetent.
As for Wei Yun,
if I hadn't helped him
in secret,
how could he
have killed Su Can?
I don't kill you
because I don't want Yue to become
estranged from me because of you.
Moreover,
do you think that you still have
any reputation in Great Sui
as the Eldest Princess?
You are nothing
but a rootless duckweed.
You took three cities
from Great Sui.
I can also turn North Qi
upside down,
never to have peace.
A grand wedding, is it?
Your Highness, don't be sad.
If the King wants to be a ruler,
he has to pay some price.
His heart towards you has never changed.
Go tell him
that I'm ill.
What?
I asked you to send for him.
Whether he comes or not is his business,
but if you don't pass the message,
and one day he asks,
it will be your fault.
Can you bear that?
Zhao Yue,
you chose this path yourself,
and you must bear
all the consequences.
What's wrong with you, Changming?
You're fine.
I heard from the Queen Mother
that you're getting married today.
I haven't spoiled your joy, have I?
You already know everything.
It's tiring to talk with my head up.
Sit down.
I don't want
to repeat myself.
Sit down.
Yes.
I know you're getting married today,
but what if
I want you
to stay with me tonight?
I'm marrying Noble Consort Chen
to gain the support of the City Lords.
Changming,
it's not easy to stabilize
the court of North Qi.
You used to ask me
why I never touched you.
It's because I like you.
But the man I like
is the you in the past.
If you're no longer pure,
I won't like you anymore.
No.
I can still be the man you like.
Is that so?
But as the King of North Qi,
you can't even choose
your bedmate tonight.
How can you still be
the man you once were?
Your Highness,
Noble Consort Chen
has sent for the King.
If you want to leave,
I won't force you.
But if you stay,
I have a gift
for you.
Send her people away.
What gift do you have for me?
Of course,
it's our wedding night.
(Marquis of Zhenguo's Mansion)
(Defend the Nation and the Throne)
I don't understand
what Shilan is thinking.
Now, the Emperor appoints him
as the General of the West
in charge of the military affairs
of Qingzhou and Fengling.
This is clearly intentional.
Yet he actually accepted the decree.
Today, Yun and I
were planning to visit the Duke of Hu,
but the Emperor's decree
has put the Wei and Song families
on opposite sides.
Yun,
are you really not angry
about what Shilan did?
Shilan deserves his promotion
for taking back Qingzhou.
I'm just curious
why the Emperor issued the decree
at this time.
In that case,
let's not just sit here.
Shilan should be back by now.
I'll go ask him myself.
Your Lordship,
General Song has brought some soldiers.
They're outside now.
(Marquis of Zhenguo's Mansion)
As soon as you were promoted,
you brought men to surround my mansion.
Did I
misjudge you,
or does power really blind you
so that you've lost your true self?
You know how much
the people admire you now,
yet you still do such absurd things.
Is this really your true nature?
Shilan,
what are you doing?
This is Yun's mansion.
Yun is our friend.
Tell your men to leave.
Wenchang.
If he can't handle
such a small situation,
how can he be the Marquis of Zhenguo?
Young Marquis Wei,
do you still remember
that you are the Marquis of Zhenguo?
My behavior
is none
of your business.
As the General of the West,
by the Emperor's verbal decree,
I'll escort Wei Yun
to the Arsenal Bureau.
You're not to leave without summons.
If you defy the decree,
you'll be defying the Emperor.
Song Shilan,
Yun gave you a chance to earn merits.
How can you do this to him?
Young Marquis Wei hasn't spoken yet.
How can you presume
to speak on his behalf?
Wenchang,
you should know the consequences
of defying an imperial decree.
The Arsenal Bureau
is not a dangerous place.
Why would I defy the decree?
Or perhaps
you want me to defy it,
so you can earn the reputation
of being loyal and dutiful.
I have a few words
to say to my family.
You surely can wait
for just a moment, right?
Yun,
are you really going to go?
Yu, you must stop him!
General,
this seems to go against the rules.
In Huajing City,
force should not be used lightly.
If the Marquis is willing to cooperate,
I will grant him this favor.
Yes.
Come here.
Have you also believed
those slanderous words,
thinking that Yun has failed
the Emperor's trust
and is unfit to be the Marquis?
Song Wenchang,
I am your brother.
Now, you question me for an outsider.
Don't you find that ridiculous?
You are my brother,
but I also risked my life for Yun.
I side with justice, not kinship.
You know Yun
has done nothing wrong,
yet you'll still lock him up
in the Bureau.
What are you thinking?
Wenchang,
why are you still so naive?
You know the consequences
of defying the Emperor.
How the Emperor treats the Weis now
is how he will treat us in the future.
Even so,
you'd still
stand up for Yun,
right?
The position of the General of the West
is both a ladder to success
and a death warrant for me.
But no matter how hard it is,
I will hold it firmly
in my hands.
Song Shilan,
I truly don't understand you.
How could you sacrifice a brother
for fame and rank?
Yes.
You never understood me
because
you never wanted to.
I've come this far step by step;
I won't stop for anyone.
Wenchang,
if you want to stop me,
go ahead.
I'd love to see
if you have the ability to do so.
Yu, I...
I know.
This is not a dead end.
We will surely find a way out.
If the road ahead is full of thorns,
let's cut through them.
You and I are each other's swords.
Even if the sky falls,
I will face it with you.
I'm willing to face it with you.
Wei Qiu,
while I'm away,
I leave the family in your hands.
I will not fail
your trust in me.
Young Marquis Wei.
(Marquis of Zhenguo's Mansion)
It's getting late.
It's time to leave.
I'll wait for your return.
You won't have to wait long.
(Marquis of Zhenguo's Mansion)
Is it really worth it
to risk yourself and the entire family
for the sake of love?
Enough nonsense.
Aren't you supposed
to take me to the Bureau?
Lead the way.
(Marquis of Zhenguo's Mansion)
Yu,
will Yun really be okay
this time?
I believe in him.
Where is Zhao Yue?
Why haven't I seen him
since I got up today?
The King went to court
early this morning.
Before leaving, he instructed
that you must wait for him to return
and have lunch together.
There's still some time before lunch.
I'd like to take a walk in the garden.
Go fetch the pomegranate dress
that Zhao Yue gave me.
I think the true red color
will complement my makeup today.
According to the rules of North Qi,
only the Queen
is permitted to dress in true red.
Please do not make it hard for us.
Didn't Zhao Yue say
that only by wearing that dress
can I leave this Palace?
The Queen Mother has decreed:
This woman disregards the palace rules
and confuses the ruler.
Take her down.
Yes.
(King's Order)
The King said
the Eldest Princess is
a distinguished guest.
(King's Order)
Without his permission,
no one can be rude to her.
Hurry up and leave.
How dare you come to accuse me?
On the wedding night,
she made you snub Noble Consort Chen.
She's causing chaos in the harem.
How can I keep her?
This is my decision.
Punish me if you want.
What does it have to do with Changming?
What kind of attitude is this?
Li Changming is up to no good.
It is already leniency
that I do not kill her.
And she dares to dress
in true red,
parading around.
I gave her that dress.
Everything was with my permission.
I've told you this many times.
Indulging in love will lead to mistakes.
The political situation
is not yet stable.
We still need
the City Lords to fight for you.
You are now the King of North Qi.
The King?
I am so restricted everywhere.
I'm not like the King at all.
Even the beggars are freer than I am.
You tell me you've prepared
everything for me,
but I feel like
I am truly
empty-handed now.
Am I your son?
No.
Power and authority
are your true sons.
I am just a pawn,
a puppet
in your hand.
You told me not to hate you,
but do you really love me?
Yue.
If I do not love you,
why did I let you
sit on this throne?
Without this throne,
who can you protect?
Think about it yourself.
Mother,
all that's left by my side is Changming.
I will never let her go.
Whether it's court affairs
or taking consorts,
I've done
everything you want me to.
But please, Mother,
do not harm Changming.
Then you should consummate
with Noble Consort Chen sooner.
As long as the City Lord of Xuan
does not come to trouble me,
of course,
I will not trouble
Li Changming.
Go see Noble Consort Chen now.
I will not pursue
the matter of today.
Alright.
I agree.
Bring them back.
And tell Li Changming
that the King is busy today
and will not go see her.
(I will not always)
(be so controlled by others.)
The Queen Mother has summoned us back.
No need to arrest her for now.
Let's go.
Your Highness,
the King said
that no matter what,
he will not wrong you.
One day,
he'll surely make you legitimate
to dress in true red.
I hope so.
♪If not for dreams by windswept flight♪
♪How would my hand find yours tonight?♪
♪This moonlit glow, in dusk's soft veil♪
♪Hears heartbeats tell their secret tale♪
♪Thoughts ablaze like beacon's fire♪
♪Outline your form in golden lyre♪
♪Through thorns we've trod and trials passed♪
♪Each grief and joy forever cast♪
♪Let the fierce warmth within your gaze♪
♪Melt this war-torn world's cruel maze♪
♪Still through the frost, I'll walk with you♪
♪Our mountains and our streams anew♪
♪Dawns greet the spring we longed to see♪
♪Through meadows where wild larks soar free♪
♪Let countless sails cross this worldly tide♪
♪When lonely shadows turn to two♪
♪Through countless turns and all we've borne♪
♪No regret ever could be sworn♪
♪Dawns greet the spring we longed to see♪
♪Beneath heaven's vault, in harmony♪
♪Let tears now fall for yesterday's strife♪
♪We've reached this blossom-covered hill♪
♪I'll follow you through every dream♪